{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Kělè",
      "answer": "可乐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuěbì",
      "answer": "雪碧"
    },
    {
      "question": "Píjiǔ",
      "answer": "啤酒"
    },
    {
      "question": "Niúnǎi",
      "answer": "牛奶"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hànbǎo",
      "answer": "汉堡"
    },
    {
      "question": "Règǒu",
      "answer": "热狗"
    },
    {
      "question": "Miànbāo",
      "answer": "面包"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhōngcān",
      "answer": "中餐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xīcān",
      "answer": "西餐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Chá",
      "answer": "茶"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mǐfàn",
      "answer": "米饭"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nǚ'ér",
      "answer": "女儿"
    },
    {
      "question": "Érzi",
      "answer": "儿子"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wǎnshàng",
      "answer": "晚上"
    },
    {
      "question": "Diàn",
      "answer": "店"
    }
  ]
}
